http://www.phonejoan.co.uk/privacy-cookie-statements/

PHONEJOAN Ltd PRIVACY POLICY
Created 24th May 20181.  IntroductionIn May 2018 a new European law called the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) came into force.  The purpose of this law is to give people more control over how organisations use their data. In accordance with GDPR we have created a Privacy Policy which provides you with details of how PhoneJoan collects, stores and uses your personal data.PhoneJoan Ltd is the data controller (referred to as “we”, “us” or “our” in this privacy notice) and we are responsible for your personal data.Name of Legal Entity: PhoneJoan LtdEmail Address: joan@phonejoan.co.ukPostal Address: 33 Tamworth Drive, Fleet, Hampshire, GU51 2UWTelephone Number: 01252 612033The GDPR applies to ‘personal data’ meaning any information relating to an identifiable person who can be directly or indirectly identified. We will act in accordance with current legislation and meet current best practice with regard to the processing of personal data.  It is very important that the information we hold about you is accurate and up to date.  Please let us know if at any time your personal information changes by emailing us at joan@phonejoan.co.uk.2. Data we collect about you In order for PhoneJoan to provide a service we require your name, address, telephone numbers, email address and various specific details depending on the service we are providing (e.g. bank details in some cases).By providing such information you consent to its use and storage in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy3.  How we collect data about youInformation is collected in several ways, e.g. by telephone, email, website enquiry form or in person during an initial meeting.4.  Reason for data being collectedWe keep data simply to help us  to help you.  5.  How the data will be usedPhoneJoan shall only use your data for the purposes for which it is provided, typically to contact you regarding the fulfilment of the service to which you have subscribed, e.g. provision of domestic cleaners, ironers or suppliers. We don’t use the data for marketing purposes and will not share it with third parties unless they are engaged in the provision of your service.6.  Disclosures of your personal dataWe may have to share your personal data with the parties set out below:-Service providers, e.g. cleaners, ironers and tradesmen who act on our behalfAccountant when annual accounts are prepared7.  Data SecurityData is stored securely in a  database on a computer which is protected with Antivirus software and a firewall.  A paper copy is also kept at the offices of PhoneJoan. Only the data controller (Joan Williamson) has access. Service providers will only process your data on our instructions and they must keep it confidential.Backups are stored with LiveDrive in the UK who have their own GDPR compliant Privacy policy.8.  Storage of personal dataIn accordance with UK Tax laws PhoneJoan will retain  the personal data it holds for at least 6 years after you stop being a customer.  We are required to retain basic information including Contact, Identity, Financial and Transaction Data.9.  Your Legal RightsWe are obliged to supply you, on request, with a copy of the personal data we hold about you.   If you wish to exercise this right, please contact us via email to joan@phonejoan.co.uk. Should you discover any inaccuracies in such personal information, please notify us as soon as possible and we will then correct our records.Cookie PolicyThis website uses cookies to enhance the user experience. Cookies are small text files that are automatically placed on your computer when you visit websites. The vast majority of websites on the internet use cookies.The purpose of our cookies is to make the website function correctly, to personalise the website to your preferences, and to collect information about your visit which will help us improve the website in the future. We never collect information that could identify you, or pass information to any third parties.You can normally visit this website without identifying who you are or revealing any information about yourself. However, cookies are used to store small amounts of information on your computer, which allows certain information from your web browser to be collected. Cookies are widely used on the internet and do not identify the individual using the computer, just the computer being used. Cookies and other similar technology make it easier for you to log on to and use our website during future visits.By using and browsing this website, you consent to cookies being used. If you do not consent, you must disable cookies in your browser or refrain from using the site.Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.In addition, we use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at  www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.
Request a Callback
Contact Name
Telephone
Email Address
Details of your enquiry
Send
PhoneJoan Ltd
33 Tamworth DriveFleetHampshireGU51 2UWCompany Registration No. 06015894
© PhoanJoan Ltd
Privacy & Cookie Statement
Web Design by Blue Room IT
